# ISHA MHATRE



#### **About Me**

Hello, I'm Isha Mhatre, UX Designer from Pune, India. To me, UX design is about humanizing technology. I strive to create seamlessly intuitive experiences to make life simpler for everybody. I've always considered people to be at the heart of the design process and I believe that creative collaboration between design and technology is the magic that takes experiences from good to great! I'm currently a 8thsemester student, pursuing my bachelor's degree in User Experience Design from MIT ID, Pune. I think when we understand human-human interaction, only then can we design efficient human-technology interaction.

I love having conversations with different people; I think that helps me communicate with my team efficiently and bring a surge of energy to every project I work on.

## **Experience**

TCS Research and Innovation Jan 2023 - June 2023 Ongoing Graduation Internship

#### Madad.info

May 2022 - July 2022 Summer Internship Role: To design and develop scalable MVP, focusing on organizations in Maharashtra.

### **Education**

#### 2017

Completed 10th(CBSE) from City International School, Kothrud, Pune with 9.8 CGPA

#### 2017-2019

Completed 12th from Dr. Kalmadi Shamarao Junior College, Pune in Science Stream and IT as optional with 70%

#### 2019-2023

Pursuing Bachelor of design degree in User Experience from MIT Institute of Design, Pune

Currently in 4th year (7.88 CGPA)

# Compentency

UX Research . Design Thinking . Wireframing . Rapid prototyping . Usability testing . Contextual Inquiry . Journey mapping . Information architecture . Problem solving . Interaction design. Competitive analysis

#### 8484908158

ishasmhatre@gmail.com ishamhatre.github.io